Finding Aid for the Preston Sturges Papers LSC.1114
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - Barbier, Pierre, M.D., 11 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Barrett, Grace., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Barrett, Grace., 11 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Barzini, Eleanor Post., 11 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 16)
    See also: Hutton, Eleanor Post [Box 98, folders 23-34].
  - Barzini, Eleanor Post., 15 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Be - Ben., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Be - Ben., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Be - Ben., 16 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Beauchamp, Anthony., 3 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Beer, Estelle., 8 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 22)
    See also: Mudge, Estelle, [Box 99, folders 23-32].
  - Beer, Estelle., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Beer, Estelle., 15 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Beer, Estelle., 13 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Beer, Estelle., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Beer, Estelle., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Beer, Estelle., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Beer, Estelle., 11 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Bell, Charles., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Bell, Charles., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Bell, Charles., 9 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Bennett, Compton., 5 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Benton, Julia and Rita., 11 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Bep - Bh., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Bep - Bh., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Bep - Bh., 17 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Bercovici, Konrad., 1 piece. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Beresford, Evelyn., 12 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Beresford, Evelyn., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Beresford, Evelyn., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Beresford, Evelyn., 13 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Bessy, Maurice., 15 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Biden, Edmund (family)., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    See also: [Box 97, folders 24-28].
  - Biden, Edmund (family)., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Biden, Edmund (family)., 15 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Biden, Edmund., 4 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Biden, Sydney., 12 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 16)
    See also: [Box 97, folders 29-31].
  - Billings Hospital, University of Chicago., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Bj - B1., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Bj - B1., 12 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Bloch, Robert, M.D., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Bloch, Robert, M.D., 6 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Blore, Eric., 8 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Bn - Bo., 11 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Bn - Bo., 11 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Bn - Bo., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Bn - Bo., 11 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Bn - Bo., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Bn - Bo., 11 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Bobbs - Merrill Company., 8 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Bodne, Benjamin B., 6 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Boeris, Joseph., 12 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Boeris, Joseph., 11 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Bourgeois, Maria-Theresa., 15 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Boyer, Charles., 1 piece. (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Boylan, Malcolm Stuart., 7 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Bra - Bri., 10 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Bra - Bri., 12 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Bra - Bri., 11 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Bracken, Eddie., 8 pieces. (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Bradbury, Ray., 1 piece. (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Breen, Joseph I., 1 piece. (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Brent, Delmar J., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Brent, Delmar J., 11 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Brewster, Margaret., 12 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Brewster, Margaret., 11 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Brewster, Margaret., 8 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Brice, Monte., 2 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Britton, Barbara., 1 piece. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Bro., 12 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Bro., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Bro., 16 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Brody, Iles., 12 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Brody, Iles., 11 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Brooke, Hillary., 1 piece. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Bru - Bz., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Bru - Bz., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Bru - Bz., 12 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Bruce, Nigel., 3 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Buckingham, Jan., 2 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Busch, Noel., 3 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - C - Cg., 12 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - C - Cg., 11 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - C - Cg., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - C - Cg., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - C - Cg., 11 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - C - Cg., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - C - Cg., 12 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - C - Cg., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - C - Cg., 8 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Cagney, James., 1 piece. (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Calibo, Leo., 14 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Agreement., 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 31)
    See also: [Box 97, folder 46].
  - California Pictures Corporation. Correspondence., 1944-1947.; 16 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Correspondence., 1944-1947.; 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Correspondence., 1944-1947.; 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Correspondence., 1944-1947.; 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Correspondence., 1944-1947.; 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Correspondence., 1944-1947.; 17 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Financial Statements and Invoices., 13 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Financial Statements and Invoices., 10 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - California Pictures Corporation. Financial Statements and Invoices., 9 pieces. (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - California State Franchise Tax Board., 5 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - California Yacht Club., 9 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Callis, D.M., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Callis, D.M., 8 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Carey, Alida., 11 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Carey, Alida., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Carlson, Erik., 12 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Carlson, Erik., 9 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Carmichael, Hoagy., 2 items. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Carter, Sidney., 4 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Cashy, Milton., 11 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Cashy, Milton., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Cashy, Milton., 12 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Cashy, Milton., 12 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Cashy, Milton., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Cashy, Milton., 15 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Ch., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Ch., 12 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Ch., 11 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Ch., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Ch., 12 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Ch., 11 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Ch., 7 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Chandlee, Harry., 5 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Chaplin, Charles & Oona., 4 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Charlot, Andre., 1 piece. (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Charmel, Andre., 11 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Charmel, Andre., 12 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Churchill, Sarah., 1 piece. (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Ci- Cn., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Ci- Cn., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Ci- Cn., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Ci- Cn., 17 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Cinematheque de Belgique., 1 piece. (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Cinematheque Francaise., 2 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Clair, Rene, 11 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Close, Harry B., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Close, Harry B., 11 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Close, Harry B., 8 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Coa - Col., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Coa - Col., 10 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Coa - Col., 12 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Coa - Col., 13 pieces. (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - Cobb, Irvin., 2 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Coburn, Charles., 3 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Cohn, Harry., 13 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Collier, Constance., 1 piece. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Collins, Victor., 12 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Collins, Victor., 12 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Colman, Ronald., 4 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Colombe, Paul de Sainte., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Colombe, Paul de Sainte., 13 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - CBS News., 7 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Pictures Corporation., 1 piece. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Com - Con., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Com - Con., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Com - Con., 15 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Condon, Richard., 7 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Conlin, Jimmy., 16 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Contin, Nick., 16 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Cod - Cor., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Cod - Cor., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Cod - Cor., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Cod - Cor., 13 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Cord, E.C., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Cord, E.C., 8 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Cornell, Katharine., 3 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Cos - Coz., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Cos - Coz., 17 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Cozzens, James G., 2 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Cr - Cz., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Cr - Cz., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Cr - Cz., 14 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Crowther, Bosley., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Crowther, Bosley., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Crowther, Bosley., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Cruban Machine & Steel Corporation., 10 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Cruban Machine & Steel Corporation., 13 pieces. (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Da., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Da., 11 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Da., 12 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Da., 14 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Danova, Cesare:, 2 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Dantine, Helmut., 3 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Dauchy, Marion Sturges., 4 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Davis, Robert A., 3 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - De Acosta, Mercedes., 5 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - De Bell, Joseph., 7 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - De Casseres, Benjamin., 2 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - de Grandcourt, Charles., 4 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Demarest, William., 4 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Denizli, Jean Jacques., 4 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 11 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 11 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 11 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Denizli, Veli Bey., 12 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - De., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - De., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - De., 12 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - De., 12 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - De., 14 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Desti, Mary., 13 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 28)
    See also: [Box 98, folders 2-3].
  - Desti, Mary., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Desti, Mary., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Desti, Mary., 11 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Desti, Mary., 12 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Desti, Mary., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - Desylva, B.G., 7 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Detitta, Arthur A., 1 piece. (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Deval, Jacques., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - Di., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - Di., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - Dietrich, Marlene., 1 piece. (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - Do., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - Do., 11 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - Do., 10 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - Do., 14 pieces. (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - Dolley, Dr. Francis S., 7 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Domergue, Faith., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Donner, Cecile., 10 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Dorfman, Sidney., 2 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Dorrance, Gordon., 7 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Doubleday, Doran & Company Incorporated., 5 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Doucede, Roger., 5 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Doucet, Catharine., 2 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Douglas, Helen G. & Melvyn., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Dozier, William., 3 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Dr - Dz., 11 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Dr - Dz., 16 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Duggan, Pat., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Duncan, Anna., 4 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Duncan, Augustin & Margherita., 6 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Duncan, Ray., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Dunne, Philip., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Dupont, E.A., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Durant, Will., 2 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Duvivier, Julien., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - E - El., 10 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - E - El., 15 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - E - El., 16 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Eddy, June., 9 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Edwards, Murphy & Minton., 11 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight., 3 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Em - Er., 10 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Em - Er., 15 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Epstein, Mel., 1 piece. (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Erskin, Chester., 3 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Es - Ez., 10 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Es - Ez., 13 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Evans, Earle W., 12 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Fa., 11 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Fa., 11 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Famous Artists Corporation., 15 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Famous Artists Corporation., 15 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Fe., 14 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Fe., 11 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Fe., 13 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Fealy, Maud., 9 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Feldkamp, Fred & Phyllis., 8 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Festival International du Film., 3 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Feuchtwanger, Lion., 2 pieces. (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Fi., 11 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Fi., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Fi., 18 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Field, Betty Sturges., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Fields, Joe., 1 piece. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Firestone, Eddie., 8 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Finkler & Finkler., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Finkler & Finkler., 17 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Fl., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Fl., 9 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Flaherty, Pat., 4 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Flippen, Jay C., 1 piece. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Florey, Robert., 1 piece. (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Fo., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Fo., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Fo., 11 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Fo., 9 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Fontaine, Joan., 2 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Ford, John., 1 piece. (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Forde, Winifred., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Forde, Winifred., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Fowler, Gene., 2 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Fox Film Corporation Studio., 8 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Francen, Victor., 1 piece. (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Fra - Pre., 11 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Fra - Fre., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Fra - Pre., 12 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Frazier, George., 3 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Freeman, Frank (Paramount)., 14 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Freeman, Mona., 1 piece. (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - French, Samuel Incorporated., 6 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Freund, Karl., 1 piece. (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Fri - Fz., 10 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Fri - Fz., 17 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Furthman, Jules., 2 pieces. (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Ga., 14 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Ga., 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Ga., 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Ga., 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Gauthier, Jacques., 4 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Gay, Marie-Noel., 14 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Ge., 11 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Ge., 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Ge., 9 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Gelb, Arthur., 2 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Gi - G1., 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Gi - G1., 12 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Gi - Gl., 9 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., n.d.; 13 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    See also: [Box 98, folders 9-10].
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1930-1932.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1930-1932.; 9 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1938-1939.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1938-1939.; 13 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1938-1939.; 11 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1938-1939.; 12 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1938-1939.; 11 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1938-1939.; 15 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1940.; 12 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1940.; 15 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1941-1942.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1941-1942.; 11 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1941-1942.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1941-1942.; 12 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1941-1942.; 11 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1943-1956.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1943-1956.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1943-1956.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1943-1956.; 10 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Gilchrist, Bianca., 1943-1956.; 16 pieces. (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., n.d.; 6 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1930-1932.; 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1930-1932.; 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1930-1932.; 4 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1930-1932.; 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1934-1936.; 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1934-1936.; 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1934-1936.; 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1934-1936.; 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1934-1936.; 13 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1937-1940.; 19 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1937-1940.; 15 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1941-1946.; 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1941-1946.; 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Gilchrist, Jack., 1941-1946.; 7 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Gillette, Edwin., 15 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Gillham, Robert M., 2 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Gleason, Jackie., 2 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Go., 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Go., 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Go., 14 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Go., 7 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Goetz, William., 1 piece. (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Gloden, John., 2 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Goldwyn, Sam and Frances., 5 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Gordon, Max., 4 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Gosden, Freeman F., 1 piece. (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Goulding, Edmund., 1 piece. (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Gra., 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Gra., 16 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Graetz, Paul., 1 piece. (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Grainger, James Edmund., 2 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Gre., 12 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Gre., 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Green, Abel (Variety)., 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Greig, Bob & Bernice., 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Gretellat, Jacques., 3 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Gri - Gru., 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Gri - Gru., 15 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Griffis, Stanton., 1 piece. (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Griffith, David W., 3 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 41)
  - Grove, Orville A., 13 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 42)
  - Grove, Orville A., 13 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 43)
  - Grove, Orville A., 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 44)
  - Grove, Orville A., 10 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 45)
  - Gw - Gz., 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 46)
  - Gw - Gz., 11 pieces. (Box 70, Folder 47)
  - Guinness, Alec., 1 piece. (Box 70, Folder 48)
  - Ha., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Ha., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Ha., 13 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Ha., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Ha., 13 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Ha., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Ha., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Ha., 11 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Ha., 9 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Hakim, Robert., 6 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Hale, Richard., 11 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Hale, Richard., 9 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Hall, Dorothy., 3 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Hall, Porter., 1 piece. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Hammerstein, Dorothy (Mrs. Oscar II)., 4 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Harris, William Jr., 9 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Harrison, Rex., 3 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Hart, Stuart., 15 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Haulman, Mildred., 15 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Hawks, William Ballinger., 2 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Hayward, Leland., 6 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - He., 11 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - He., 12 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - He., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - He., 17 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Hecht, Arnold., 3 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Heffernan, Harold., 1 piece. (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Heinreid, Paul., 2 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Henigson, Henry., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 29)
    See also: [Box 97, folders 14-18].
  - Henigson, Henry., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Henigson, Henry., 11 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Henigson, Henry., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Henigson, Henry., 11 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - Henigson, Henry., 13 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Henigson, Henry., 11 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Henigson, Henry., 10 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - Hepburn, Katharine., 3 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Herendeen, Fred., 2 pieces. (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Hersholt, Jean., 1 piece. (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 12 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 13 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 15 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 12 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Hertz, John Jr., 13 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Hervey, Barber & McKee., 11 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Heydt, Louis Jean., 4 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Hi., 14 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Hi., 11 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Hi., 11 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Hicks, Wilson., 2 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Hitchcock, Keith., 2 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Hoa - Hoo., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Hoa - Hoo., 15 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Hoa - Hoo., 14 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Hollywood Reporter., 15 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Hop - How., 10 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Hop - How., 12 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Hop - How., 9 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Hope, Bob., 1 piece. (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Hopper, Hedda., 4 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Hornblow, Arthur Jr., 3 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Houseman, John., 1 piece. (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Houser, Mervin Jr., 1 piece. (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Howard, Leslie. (Box 72, Folder 31)